lottomasterformula.com 2015-12-31

# About Us

We take your privacy seriously. Please review what we have committed to in order to protect your personal information.

Overview

The privacy and security of your personal information that we receive and collect from you are important to us. As such, we have set forth certain privacy and security standards that are intended to safeguard your personal information.

Information Collection, Use, Sharing and Access

1\. Information Collection

We may collect information relating to:

Contact information such as your name, email address and mobile phone number.  
Browser information such as your IP address, cookies and recorded information such your browser type, language, transactions, contributed content and the date and time of your activities.

2\. Information Use

We may combine personal information collected from you with information from third parties or other companies for providing better user experience and customized services for you.

We may use information for purposes relating to:

Customizing the content and advertising that you see  
Conducting analyses and research  
Providing/improving products and services that you've requested or that you are most active with  
Providing anonymous information to internal and external parties  
Complying with legal processes, subpoenas, court orders, prevent fraud or imminent harm, and ensuring the security of our network and services.

LottoMasterFormula.com may also use information to communicate with you information about LottoMasterFormula.com, promotions and products and services. You may opt-out of receiving non-essential communications; however, certain essential emails, which are necessary for the administration and maintenance of your account, may still be communicated with you.

3\. Information Sharing

We do not rent, sell or share your personal information with other people or companies except when we receive your permission.

In the case LottoMasterFormula.com is acquired by or merged with another company, LottoMasterFormula.com will transfer your information to the acquired or merged company. However, LottoMasterFormula.com will notify you before your information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

4\. Information Access

You have the right to view or edit your personal information yourself when you are signed into your account, or have the right to request that LottoMasterFormula.com edit the information on your behalf.

For personal information that may not be accessible via the websites, you may still access that information by writing to us by email to support@lottomasterformula.com and we will contact you within 30 days regarding your request.

You also have the right to limit certain personal information from being displayed on your user profile for the public to view. You may request that LottoMasterFormula.com limit the information for you.

We limit access to your personal information to persons under the employment of, contracted by, or managed under LottoMasterFormula.com who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with your information in order to do their jobs.

5\. Opt Out

You can opt out of any mailings from us at any time by clicking on the UNSUBSCRIBE link at the bottom of email communications we sent you.

Links

LottoMasterFormula.com may provide, or third parties may provide, links to other websites. Because LottoMasterFormula.com has no control over these sites, LottoMasterFormula.com cannot acknowledge or endorse the availability, existence or practice of any privacy policies on these external domains. We strongly encourage you to review the privacy policy of these external websites before providing your personal information. At no time will we share your personal information with these non-affiliated domains.

Use of Cookies

LottoMasterFormula.com may use "cookies" to enable you to sign in to our services. Your preference and information may be stored on the cookies in order to simplify your experience by saving you time from repeatedly entering the same information.

Cookies may also allow your e-mail address or username be pre-populated, so that you will only need to type your password the next time you sign in. If you are using a public computer or do not otherwise want this information to be stored, you can select the appropriate radio button on the sign-in page, and this cookie will not be used. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer.

Changes to Privacy Policy

We may occasionally update our privacy policy and respective statement to reflect changes in our products and services. When we post changes to this Statement, we will update the effective date at the top of this statement.

If changes to our privacy policy are material, we will notify you either by prominently posting a notice of such changes prior to implementing the change or by directly sending you a notification.

We encourage you to periodically review our privacy policy and this statement to be informed of how LottoMasterFormula.com is protecting your personal information.
